slantmagazine.com 2019-06-05

# Privacy Policy - Slant Magazine

Slantmagazine.com respects your right to the privacy of the personal information you provide us on our website. To that end, unless you designate otherwise or we state otherwise in this policy or at the time information is collected, any personal information you provide to Slantmagazine.com will be known only to two parties: you and Slantmagazine.com. The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our site and its features. Personal information includes your name, street, and email addresses, click-through activity, and any other personal information you may provide here. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.

 **Information we collect:**

1\. Across our site you will be presented with the opportunity to sign up for our Newsletter. For this we collect your email address. If you would like to unsubscribe from our communications at any time, you may do so by following the instructions in our emails.

2\. We use cookies and analytics tools across our site to collect information about you. This information can be used to improve the performance of the site, make advertising more relevant, and enhance your user experience. If you wish to manage your cookies, please follow the instructions in the “How to manage cookies” section lower on this page.

 **How we use your personal information:**

Advertising: We use third-party advertising companies (Freestar, Google AdSense) to serve ads when you visit our site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Cookies: We use cookies to understand how our customers use our site and interact with it. For example, we use technology on our site which records user movements, which pages are most popular, and how navigation options are used. This helps us to identify usability issues and improve the assistance we can provide to users and is also used for aggregated and statistical reporting purposes. We also use cookies to understand what type of device you are using to show you the best version of the site.

 **Who we share your personal information with:**

We disclose personal information to the advertising partners listed above, through cookies to collect personal information and serve you with advertisements that we believe are relevant to you and your interests.

We disclose your email address to a service provider we engage to manage our newsletter delivery. We do not rent or sell our email lists to anyone.

 **Other disclosure of personal information:**

Slantmagazine.com will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except (i) as described in this privacy policy, or (ii) as required by law, court order, or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority. This policy does not protect information you post to our site via Disqus or any other public forum within our website.

 **Other sites:**

Slantmagazine.com contains many links to other sites on the Web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other websites.

 **How to manage cookies:**

If you wish to manage your cookies, please follow the instructions below. Please remember that if you choose to disable cookies, certain sections of our site may not work properly.

You can opt out of behaviorally targeted advertising through Google [here](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

We also allow other third parties to target you based on data you have provided to them, to the extent that you have consented to this. To opt out of these cookies, please click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) for E.U. or [here](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2#!/) for U.S.

By opting out of these types of cookies on each browser and device you use, you will stop receiving advertisements that are targeted specifically to you on our site; however you will still see the same number of advertisements, which may include contextual advertisements that are not targeted based on your personal information.

You can also manage your cookies via your browser settings. For more information, please visit your browser’s help page.

 **How long we retain your personal information:**

We keep your information for no longer than necessary for the purposes for which it is processed. The length of time for which we retain information depends on the purposes for which we collected and use it and/or as required to comply with applicable laws.

 **How we protect your data:**

All communications with our site, including submission of your email address for Newsletter subscription, is encrypted using SSL (secure sockets layer).

If you have any further questions or concerns about Slantmagazine.com’s privacy policies and use of personal information, please contact us.
